[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why couldnt the couple get a loan for a respectable home in one of the freecreditreport.com commercials?", "correct_answer": "She defaulted on some old credit card.", "incorrect_answers": ["Some punk opened a credit card in her name.", "He had a poor credit score.", "His credit was whack."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which continent are common daisies native?", "correct_answer": "Europe", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "North America", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cheese is the Gorgonzola cheese?", "correct_answer": "Blue cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["White cheese", "Yellow cheese", "Creamy cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This villain was chosen for position # 33 on the AFI\u2019s list of the top movie villains. He has been in many movies but his appearance in a 1931 movie is regarded as the most memorable.", "correct_answer": "Count Dracula", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankenstein", "The Devil", "The Alien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who graduated from Yale University in 1991, received a Golden Globe for his role in 1996 movie Primal Fear.", "correct_answer": "Edward Norton", "incorrect_answers": ["Ron Livingston", "Matt Damon", "Ed Burns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Tim Burton movies stars Johnny Depp?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Big Fish", "Planet of the Apes", "Mars Attacks!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The piece known as the noyon is found in this version of chess.", "correct_answer": "shatar", "incorrect_answers": ["makruk", "xiangqi", "chaturanga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a fluid?", "correct_answer": "A gas or a liquid", "incorrect_answers": ["A gas", "A liquid", "Anything that can produce energy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What comic book is The Human Torch from?", "correct_answer": "Fantastic Four", "incorrect_answers": ["X-Men", "Daredevil", "The Incredible Hulk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the beleaguered family in the horror movie Poltergeist?", "correct_answer": "Freeling", "incorrect_answers": ["Wiseman", "Lucus", "Nelson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many moons, revolving around Jupiter, did Galileo Galilei discover in the 17th century?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["9", "1", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the slow loris, a primate which is both poisonous and venomous?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It covers its young with a toxin to keep them from being eaten.", "It has a venomous bite.", "It secretes a toxin from the glands on the inside of its elbows."]}]